Branden Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in

github.com/BrandenDaniel 🖸

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

J 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fiery passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautifully spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I have crafted outstanding websites that have wowed clients and peers, boasting professionally structured and understandable code. I am currently learning React/Next.js and API integrations.

Experience

LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present

Melbourne CBD, VIC / Hybrid

Front-end Web Developer

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients and governments across Australia.

- Maintain proprietary leasing/salary packaging software with clean & structured front-end code. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)
- Maintain and manage LeasePLUS's websites (salarypackagingplus.com.au, Leaseplus.com.au)

LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer - salary deductions receivable & payable

Apr. 2022 - Sept. 2022 Melbourne CBD, VIC

Arcadian Digital &

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Melbourne CBD, VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian delivers tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes.

- Collaborative work with project managers/senior developers, producing smart and intuitive solutions
- Build and structure WordPress reusable child themes
- Build and maintain company's own WordPress plugins and themes

Bebble Media &

May. 2018 - Jun. 2019

North Laverton, VIC

Junior Front-end Web Developer

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

- · Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

Tech Stack & Skills Interests & Hobbies React.js | Next.js | JavaScript | HTML CSS ETFs & Index Funds | Personal Finance Tech Sass | jQuery | Git | API integration Critically Acclaimed Films | Youtube Work **Personal Projects** MySalPack & 2023 My Web Portfolio 🔗 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | Sass Blazor Bootstrap React | JavaScript | HTML Sass Print Strategy Management & 2019 Coffeeroasters & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | WordPress Bootstrap React | Next.js | JavaScript CSS Sass Kader Boot Co. 6 2019 Cryptoverse & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | WordPress Bootstrap CSS React | Redux | Rapid API | Sass Ant Design

Education

Udacity

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Oct. 2017 - May 2018

May - Aug. 2017

Online

Online

Jul. 2016 — Apr. 2017

Melbourne, VIC

Front End Web Development Track

RMIT University

Team Treehouse

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology Relevant Courses Included:

Web Programming

User-centered Design